WHY IS EVERYBODY USING
THESE TINY LITTLE LIGHTS
NOWADAYS?
I REMEMBER WHEN PEOPLE
USED TO USE BIG LIGHTS.
THAT'S A GOOD
STORY, GRANDPA.
HEY.
All:
WOW.
MONICA'S LETTING OTHER PEOPLE
HELP DECORATE HER TREE.
DID SOMEONE
GET HER DRUNK AGAIN?
HAVING A PERFECTLY
DECORATED TREE
IS NOT WHAT
CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT.
IT'S ABOUT BEING WITH
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE.
THAT IS NICE
AND WE'RE DONE, TA-DA!
Chandler:
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IT JUST DOESN'T QUITE FEEL
LIKE CHRISTMAS TO ME.
OH, YEAH.
NOW IT FEELS
LIKE CHRISTMAS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
AND THAT'S THE STORY
OF THE DREIDEL.
NOW, SOME PEOPLE TRACE
THE CHRISTMAS TREE
BACK TO THE EGYPTIANS
WHO USED TO BRING
GREEN PALM BRANCHES
INTO THEIR HUTS
ON THE SHORTEST DAY OF THE YEAR
SYMBOLIZING LIFE'S TRIUMPH
OVER DEATH
AND THAT WAS, LIKE,
4,000 YEARS AGO.
SO PRETTY MUCH
AROUND THE SAME TIME
YOU STARTED TELLING THIS STORY.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOE,
WHAT'S UP?
I HAD TO GET OUT
OF THE APARTMENT.
JANINE IS, LIKE,
STRETCHING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
EVERYWHERE I LOOK,
SHE'S, LIKE...
I CAN SEE WHY THAT'S
HARD TO RESIST.
I LIKE HER SO MUCH!
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE
THAT SHE DOESN'T FEEL
THE SAME WAY.
SHE'S SO SWEET.
I JUST WANT TO FEED HER GRAPES
AND BRUSH HER HAIR.
YOU ARE AWARE THAT SHE'S
NOT A MONKEY, RIGHT?
I AM SO OVER JANINE.
I MEAN...
AT FIRST, I THOUGHT SHE WAS HOT
BUT NOW, SHE'S LIKE, OLD NEWS.
HI, GUYS.
JANINE!
COFFEE TO GO, PLEASE.
I JUST GOT A CALL
TO BE A DANCER
ON A TELEVISION SPECIAL
FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE.
IT'S CALLED SOME SORT OF
"DICKIN' ROCKIN' DICKIE EVE."
HOLD IT.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
DICK CLARK'S
NEW YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE?
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
OH, MY GOD!
WE LOVE THAT SHOW.
ROSS AND I HAVE
BEEN WATCHING IT
SINCE I CAN REMEMBER.
YOU'RE STILL JUST
A LITTLE FAT GIRL INSIDE
AREN'T YOU?
I'LL BE ON IT THIS YEAR.
I'LL BE ONE
OF THE PARTY PEOPLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
A PARTY PERSON?!
THOSE GUYS ROCK THE MOST!
THEY SAID I SHOULD
BRING SOMEONE.
DO YOU WANT TO BE
MY DANCE PARTNER?
TOTALLY!
I WOULD LOVE TO SPEND
NEW YEAR'S WITH YOU.
ACTUALLY, THEY'RE TAPING
TOMORROW.
I DON'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND WHY.
HOW IT WORKS IS
THE PART WITH DICK CLARK
IN TIMES SQUARE
IS ACTUALLY LIVE
BUT THEY TAPE SOME OF
THE PARTY STUFF AHEAD OF TIME.
NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE KNOW THAT.
DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO COME, TOO?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WE ARE THERE.
( laughing )
WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?
WELL, I USED TO DATE HIM
BUT YOU'RE STILL
GOING OUT WITH HER.
OH, THANKS.
GREAT. SO WE CAN
ALL GO TOGETHER.
WELL, I'LL
CATCH YOU LATER.
BYE, JANINE.
DID SHE JUST ASK ME OUT
ON A DATE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
SHE JUST INVITED HIM TO
THE BIGGEST PARTY
OF THE MILLENNIUM.
YEAH, BUT SHE ALSO INVITED
YOU AND ROSS.
HONEY, I'M SORRY
BUT I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
A ROMANTIC THING.
I KNOW HOW I CAN FIND OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO A NEW YEAR'S EVE
PARTY, RIGHT?
AT MIDNIGHT, I CAN KISS HER.
IF SHE KISSES ME BACK, GREAT.
BUT IF SHE SAYS, "DUDE,
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?"
I CAN SAY, "IT WASN'T ME;
IT WAS NEW YEAR'S."
THAT'S A LOT BETTER THAN ROSS
TRYING TO KISS ME IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND SAYING THAT HE DID IT
BECAUSE HE NEEDED CHAPSTICK.
IT WAS A DRY DAY.
WE ARE GOING TO
DICK CLARK'S NEW YEAR'S
ROCKIN' EVE!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, NOW LISTEN UP.
I'VE BEEN ON SETS BEFORE.
LET ME GIVE YOU
A LITTLE ADVICE.
IT'S A SHOW,
BUT WE'RE JUST DANCING.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
THE IMPORTANT THING
TO REMEMBER:
STAY COOL.
GOT IT.
OH, MY GOD,
IT'S JUST LIKE I DREAMED IT!
OKAY, EVERYONE, GATHER UP.
Monica:
EXCUSE US.
HERE'S WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
THE MUSIC WILL START,
YOU'LL DANCE.
WE'LL TAPE YOU;
DON'T LOOK AT THE CAMERA.
ANY QUESTIONS?
YEAH, I HAVE A QUESTION.
WHEN IS THIS
GOING TO AIR?
YEAH.
NOW, YOU GUYS,
DANCE OVER THERE.
YOU GUYS, OVER THERE.
I WANT YOU TWO
RIGHT AROUND HERE.
EVERYONE ELSE, SPREAD OUT.
ROSS.
SO WHEN IS IT
GOING TO AIR?
OKAY, PHEEBS, YOU LOOK
IN THE KITCHEN.
I WILL LOOK
IN THE BACK CLOSET.
I CAN SAVE YOU TIME, LADIES.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
YEAH.
CHANDLER, WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE A WALK?
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR
OUR CHRISTMAS PRESENTS
FROM MONICA.
WHAT? THAT'S TERRIBLE.
NO, WE DO IT
EVERY YEAR.
OH, WELL, THAT MAKES IT
NOT TERRIBLE.
NO, YEAH. WE NEVER FIND THEM.
SHE'S ALWAYS BESTED US,
THAT WILY... MINX.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO SEARCH HERE
FOR AN HOUR
AND THEN WE'LL GO OVER TO JOEY'S
AND SEARCH, OKAY?
NO, NOT OKAY.
YOU CAN'T LOOK FOR
MONICA'S PRESENTS.
WE HAVE TO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO,
AND YOU CAN'T
BECAUSE I LIVE HERE, TOO.
WELL, THEN, YOU SHOULD
LOOK WITH US.
WHY?
AREN'T YOU WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT TO GET
MONICA FOR CHRISTMAS?
I HAVE A GREAT IDEA
FOR A PRESENT FOR HER.
( scoffing ):
THAT'S IT, "A GREAT IDEA"?
CHANDLER,
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
WHAT IF SHE GETS YOU
A GREAT PRESENT
TWO MEDIUM PRESENTS
AND THEN A BUNCH
OF LITTLE PRESENTS
AND YOU'VE JUST GOTTEN HER
ONE GREAT PRESENT?
THAT'S JUST GOING TO
MAKE HER FEEL BAD.
WHY WOULD YOU
DO THAT TO
HER, CHANDLER?
IF I HELPED
WE COULD FIND THEM FASTER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
OOH, WE HAVE A LIVE ONE.
IT'S A MACY'S BAG.
YEAH.
OOH, WHO'S IT FOR?
"DEAR LOSERS, DO YOU
REALLY THINK
I'D HIDE PRESENTS
UNDER THE COUCH?"
"P.S.: CHANDLER, I KNEW
THEY'D BREAK YOU."
UH-OH. SHE MAY BE ON TO US.
WE ARE SO GOING TO FIND THEM
THIS YEAR.
YOU SAID YOU WERE
GOING ACROSS THE
HALL AND LOOK.
YOU DON'T DO THAT
EVERY YEAR, DO YOU?
YEAH.
YOU DON'T, LIKE
GO INTO THE BACK
OF MY CLOSET
AND LOOK UNDER
MY GYM BAG OR ANYTHING.
NO. WE NEVER DO THAT.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE JOEY
GAVE ME SOME STUFF TO STORE
THAT I'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE
IN MY LIFE.
OKAY, THAT DID NOT JUST HAPPEN.
OKAY, HERE COMES
ANOTHER CAMERA.
RIGHT. NO BIGGIE;
STAY LOOSE.
WHY DO THEY
KEEP DOING THAT?
IF WE WANT TO GET ON CAMERA
WE HAVE TO GET ON
ONE OF THOSE PLATFORMS.
THEY'VE BEEN TAPING
THOSE PEOPLE ALL DAY.
RIGHT.
HEY, WHAT DID YOU GUYS DO
TO GET UP ON THERE?
WE LEARNED HOW TO DANCE.
OH, YEAH?
WHEN YOU LEARNED
HOW TO DANCE
DID YOU FORGET HOW TO
PUT ON UNDERPANTS?
YEAH.
HEY, YOU'RE
A GOOD DANCER.
REALLY?
YOU'D BE BETTER IF YOU
LOOSENED YOUR HIPS A LITTLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, LIKE THIS.
THAT'S IT.
JUST FEEL THE RHYTHM.
THAT'S BETTER.
( falsetto ):
UH-HUH.
YOU'RE DANCING
WITH THAT GIRL THERE.
NO, NO, NO.
WE CAME TOGETHER.
I DON'T SEE IT.
YOU ARE DANCING WITH
THE TALL GUY OVER THERE.
TALL GUY,
RAISE YOUR HAND.
PLEASE LET ME
DANCE WITH THAT GIRL.
I REALLY LIKE HER
AND I THINK I
HAVE A SHOT.
REALLY? YOU THINK SO?
I DON'T.
I COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING
AT JOEY...
HEY, WHOA, WHOA.
WE FOUND THEM.
THEY WERE IN THE GUEST ROOM
CLOSET BEHIND SOME COATS.
YEAH, AND YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT
'CAUSE THEY'RE ALL CRAP.
THOSE ARE MY GIFTS.
I GOT THOSE FOR YOU.
OH, THANKS, CHANDLER.
THEY'RE GREAT.
Rachel:
WELL, CHANDLER
THEN WHAT IS THIS VERY
WEIRD METAL "A," "Z" THING?
THOSE ARE BOOKENDS.
THAT'S A GREAT GIFT.
OH, OKAY, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU FOR MY "AZ."
MAKE SURE YOU PUT ALL THAT STUFF
BACK IN THE CLOSET, OKAY?
YES, OKAY.
OH, BY THE WAY,
I JUST GOT TO SAY
I THINK IT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU
THAT EVEN AFTER YOU'VE MOVED
YOU STILL KEEP STORING
THAT STUFF FOR JOEY.
HEY, DANCING GIRL.
CAN I... CAN I GO
TO THE BATHROOM?
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
YEAH. THERE YOU GO.
LOOKING GOOD, GELLERS.
WE KNOW.
HEY, LOOK.
YOU KNOW THAT
SNIPPY GUY OVER THERE?
HE'S THE ONE WHO DECIDES
WHO GETS ON THE PLATFORM.
WE SHOULD GO
DANCE BY HIM.
OKAY.
OKAY, EVERYBODY HOLD.
NEXT ON THE
PLATFORMS ARE...
YOU TWO.
AND...
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
WOULD IT HELP IF I WEREN'T
WEARING UNDERPANTS?
MONICA!
WOULD IT?
HEY, TALL GUY.
LISTEN, I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT THAT GIRL
THAT YOU'RE
DANCING WITH.
SHE'S NICE, HUH?
TO THINK I ALMOST
BROUGHT MY WIFE TO THIS.
YEAH, YEAH. OKAY.
UH, LOOK, BUDDY,
I CAME WITH THAT GIRL.
AND I HAD THIS PLAN
TO KISS HER
AT THE NEW YEAR'S
COUNTDOWN.
I'M TRYING TO WIN HER OVER,
YOU KNOW?
SO I WAS WONDERING...
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, COME ON, MAN.
YOU CAN DANCE
WITH MY PARTNER.
SHE'S REAL MELLOW.
LOOK, YOU DATING THIS
GIRL YOU CAME WITH?
WELL, I WAS HOPING
AFTER TONIGHT
THAT MAYBE I COULD...
NO, NO, SHE'S FAIR GAME
IF YOU ASK ME.
SORRY, BUDDY.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, YOU KNOW,
FAIR IS FAIR.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU'RE
RIGHT YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT CAN I SAY, BUT...
HEY!
GOD!
WHAT, ARE YOU IN
THE SECOND GRADE?
HEY, MAN, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WET HIS PANTS.
HEY! HEY!
HEY!
MAN, THIS SUCKS.
IF MOM AND DAD DON'T
SEE US ON TV
AFTER WE MADE THEM
SO JEALOUS
WHO'S GOING TO BE
THE LOSERS THEN?
HEY, I KNOW WHAT WILL GET
US UP ON A PLATFORM.
WHAT?
THE ROUTINE.
ROSS, WE HAVEN'T DONE
THE ROUTINE SINCE MIDDLE SCHOOL.
HEY, WHEN THE SNIPPY GUY
SEES THE ROUTINE
HE'LL WANT TO BUILD US
OUR OWN PLATFORM.
WAS IT REALLY THAT GOOD?
WE GOT HONORABLE MENTION
IN THE BROTHER/SISTER
DANCE CATEGORY.
LOOK, IT'S ALMOST
FAKE MIDNIGHT.
DO WE REALLY HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE?
OKAY, LET'S DO IT.
MOM AND DAD ARE GOING
TO BE SO FACED.
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
SO, DO WE REALLY
NEED TO ASK
WHO'S GOING UP ON
THE PLATFORM NEXT?
OH, NO.
GET UP THERE AND DO THAT
AGAIN EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
YEAH!
MAKE SURE AND GET THIS.
DICK WILL WANT IT
FOR THE BLOOPERS SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, CUT.
LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
WHEN WE START AGAIN
IT'S GOING TO BE THE
COUNTDOWN TO NEW YEAR'S
SO I WANT TO SEE
EVERYBODY'S EXCITEMENT.
HEY, GUY, YOU'VE GOT
ABOUT THREE SECONDS
TO GET AWAY
FROM MY PARTNER.
WHAT'S GOING ON
OVER HERE?
TAKE A LOOK AT
THE GUY'S PANTS, HUH?
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU TOLD US
TO SHOW EXCITEMENT
BUT DON'T YOU THINK HE WENT
A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
GET OUT OF HERE.
YEAH, TAKE A HIKE,
WET PANTS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
WE'RE GOING TO BE
ON THE PLATFORM
FOR THE MILLENNIAL MOMENT.
I KNOW.
HEY, YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN PRACTICING
THE ROUTINE,
HAVE YOU?
NO.
ME, TOO.
HEY, WHEN THE MUSIC
STARTS UP AGAIN
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
MAYBE GOING INTO THE
ROBOT, YOU KNOW.
ROSS, I THINK WE SHOULD
STICK TO THE ROUTINE.
WE DON'T WANT
TO LOOK STUPID.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE BACK.
TEN SECONDS LEFT.
HERE WE GO.
TEN...
All:
NINE...
EIGHT...
SEVEN...
Joey:
OKAY...
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THIS.
WHATEVER HAPPENS, HAPPENS.
DESTINY.
THREE...
TWO...
ONE...
CUT!
NO!
YEAR!
HAPPY NO YEAR.
HERE'S WHERE WE GO TO
THE LIVE SHOT OF TIMES SQUARE.
THAT'S A WRAP.
( quacking )
HEY, LOOK WHO I FOUND.
OH, HI, GUYS.
YOU KNOW, BIRDS HAVE A VERY GOOD
SENSE OF DIRECTION.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
THEY COULD HELP US FIND
WHERE THE PRESENTS ARE HIDDEN.
YES, IF THE PRESENTS ARE
HIDDEN SOUTH FOR THE WINTER.
OR WE COULD JUST FOLLOW
YOUR CLEVER JOKES.
ANY IDEAS? NO? DIDN'T THINK SO.
COME ON, GUYS.
SHOW US WHERE
THE PRESENTS ARE.
THE DUCK SEEMS TO THINK
THAT MONICA GOT ME GARBAGE.
HMM, I WONDER
WHAT I CAN GET MONICA
THAT'S AS GOOD AS GARBAGE?
HMM, HOW ABOUT MY "AZ"?
( knocking )
HEY, THIS IS HOLLOW.
WHAT?
THIS BENCH, IT'S HOLLOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I NEVER KNEW THAT.
OH! THE PRESENTS!
NO, DON'T LOOK
DIRECTLY AT THEM.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, NO,
WE COULD LOOK AT THEM.
OH, THIS ONE'S
FOR ME.
THIS ONE'S FOR CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
AND THE BIG ONE'S
FOR ME.
LET'S OPEN THEM.
OKAY, OKAY.
WAIT A MINUTE,
WAIT A MINUTE.
WE CAN'T DO THIS.
WHY?
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW
WHAT MONICA GOT ME.
I MEAN, LOOK, I'M SURE
SHE WORKED REALLY HARD
AT GETTING ME A PRESENT
AND WANTING TO SURPRISE ME
AND YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO RUIN THAT.
LOOK, WE HAVE
TO PUT THESE BACK.
THIS IS NOT WHAT
CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT.
WHATEVER, LINUS.
I'M OPENING MINE.
NOBODY IS OPENING ANYTHING,
OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT YOU GUYS
BUT I WANT TO SEE THE LOOK
ON MONICA'S FACE
WHEN I GIVE HER
MY PRESENT.
AND I'M SURE SHE WANTS TO SEE
THE LOOK ON MY FACE
WHEN I GET MINE.
SO PLEASE, CAN WE JUST...
CAN WE PUT THEM BACK?
WILL YOU GET US BETTER GIFTS?
FINE.
HEY, GUYS.
YOU FOUND THE PRESENTS?
CHANDLER, YOU LET
THEM FIND THE PRESENTS?
GREAT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT TOOK ME
TO FIND YOU THAT WATER PURIFIER?
THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT ME?
YES, I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
THAT LOOK IS PRICELESS.
HOME SWEET HOME, HUH?
NICE TO GET BACK
TO REALITY.
PLUS, WE KNOW HOW
THE NEW YEAR'S
GOING TO GO OFF.
I GUESS THERE'S NO REASON
FOR ALL THAT Y2K
PANIC, YOU KNOW.
ANYWAY, GOOD NIGHT.
JOEY.
YEAH?
THREE...
TWO... ONE.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
( clearing throat )
( mumbling )
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
TONIGHT WHEN THEY
YELLED CUT
AND WE DIDN'T
GET TO KISS
I WAS REALLY, REALLY
DISAPPOINTED.
AND I JUST...
I JUST REALLY WANTED
TO KISS YOU.
REALLY?
IN THE MOMENT
I REALLY WANTED
TO KISS YOU, TOO.
IN THE MOMENT.
IN THE MOMENT, HUH?
BUT ONLY IN THE MOMENT.
SO, DO YOU...
WANT TO KISS AGAIN?
SURE. NEW YEAR'S EVE
IS ONLY TWO WEEKS AWAY.
CAN YOU WAIT?
NO.
ME NEITHER.
THREE... TWO...
JOEY, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO COUNTDOWN
EVERY TIME WE KISS.
OKAY.
EXCEPT THAT I SORT OF FELT
LIKE I NEEDED
A COUPLE SECONDS
TO GET READY.
WE WERE ON THE PLATFORM
READY TO DANCE THE WORLD
INTO THE NEW MILLENNIUM
AND THE GUY YELLS "CUT."
WAIT A MINUTE,
SO YOU GUYS ARE TELLING ME
THAT YOU ACTUALLY DID
THE ROUTINE FROM EIGHTH GRADE?
YEAH.
BUT OF COURSE WE HAD TO
UPDATE IT A LITTLE BIT.
HEY, BY THE WAY, QUICK THINKING
ABOUT CATCHING ME.
YEAH, 'CAUSE I WAS GOING TO SAY
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD HAVE
DONE THE END
THE WAY YOU GUYS DID IT
BACK THEN.
WHAT?
WE COULD DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU WERE A LOT BIGGER...
I MEAN, STRONGER
BACK THEN.
I CAN DO IT, OKAY.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE...
Both:
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
I CAN'T DO IT!
NOW, YOU DO THAT,
YOU'RE ON TV.